articlemonster.com 2011-06-07

# Privacy policy - articlemonster.com

This privacy policy sets out how we use and protects any information that you give us when you use this website. We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address.

We will collect only the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our forums,(if or when we decide to use forums) the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate (non personally identifiable) information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

We respect your privacy. We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to any third parties, or are required to by law. The information we collect is only used to improve the content of our web site.

**Communications Policy:**

Article Monster.com has a no-spam email policy, however, email communication with members is critical to site operations. You should expect to receive Article Monster.com news and system updates on an as-needed basis.

**With respect to cookies:**

We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as members area login (remember me) or items that consumers add to their shopping cart. If you do not want to accept cookies, you can disable them in your browser, but if you do you may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, also we may not be able to customise the sites features according to your preferences.

**With respect to third party companies and services:**

To try and bring you offers and services that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies. Article Monster.com expects it's partners, affiliates and advertisers to respect the privacy of our users and members. However, as a result of your visit to our site, third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers may have their own data collection and privacy policies and may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information.

While on our site, our partners, advertisers or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify your preferences or retrieve information about you.

Article Monster.com does not control the use of any technology used by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties.

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information on our forums, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected by anyone without our knowledge and my result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Article Monster.com and this policy.

For further information, consult the privacy policies of:

  * www.google.com
  * www.amazon.com
  * www.amazon.ca
  * www.amazon.fr
  * www.amazon.de
  * www.amazon.co.uk
  * www.addthis.com
  * www.digg.com
  * www.linkxl.com

Or any other individuals or third parties, mentioned anywhere on this website.

**Changes to this policy:**

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our web site periodically.

**Contacting us:**

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, or have any questions relating to this policy, please [contact us](http://www.articlemonster.com/contact/)
